Guide to the Jack Lewis papers, 1915-2001.
Lewis, Jack papers,
- Personal Documents
  - Subseries Xd. Travel
    - Austria, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Includes travel programs, maps, and brochures.
    - Belgium, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Denmark, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - England and the British Isles, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 13-17)
    - England and the British Isles, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - England and the British Isles, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - France, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Germany, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Greece, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Italy, 1937-1951 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Netherlands, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - New Zealand and Australia, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
    - Scotland, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
    - Switzerland, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Travel notebooks, 1950-1960 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Florida, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Georgia, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Oklahoma, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - South Carolina, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Texas bank/mortgage, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Virginia, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - USA travel maps, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - USA travel maps and guides, 1970-1990 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
- Publications
  - Publications with articles on or by Lewis, 1950-1951 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Includes correspondence.
  - Pamphlets, newsletters, clippings, and magazines on Christianity, 1950-2002 (Box 33, Folder 4-12)
    Includes topics such as Christian Doctrine, teachings, general religion and events.
  - Pamphlets, newsletters, clippings, and magazines on Christianity, 1950-2002 (Box 34, Folder 1-9)
  - Christianity publications with list, 1950-1960 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Christianity publications with list, 1950-1960 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets, newsletters, clippings, and magazines on Christianity, 1950-2002 (Box 35, Folder 2-9)
  - Pamphlets, newsletters, clippings, and magazines on Christianity, 1950-2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Austin Seminary bulletin, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - CALC Report, 1981-1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Commonweal, 1974-1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Context, 1987-05-1988-03 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - The Ecumenist, 1964-1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - The Egg, 1981-1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Engage Social Action, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - The Free Society, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Frontier, 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Laity, 1960-1964 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - The Student World, 1946-1956 (Box 36, Folder 14-15)
  - Theology Today, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - UT Austin publications, 1950-1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Utne Reader, 1991-1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - World Council of Churches, 1950-1955 (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
  - Weavings, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - World Student Christian Federation, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
  - Netherlands schools, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 8-9)
  - British church and schools, 1950-1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Publications on cancer, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Publications on politics and rights, 1950-1962 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Publications on war and the military, 1945-1970 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Publications on family and children, 1960-1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Publications on education, 1950-1970 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
  - Publications on women, Undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Publications on drugs, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 5-6)
  - Publications on society, 1950-1970 (Box 38, Folder 7-8)
  - Publications on alcoholism, 1955-1970 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Publications on death, 1970-1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Publications on mental health, 1955-1980 (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
  - Open Prayer: prayers and other materials for the worship service, Undated (Box 38)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1950-2000 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
  - Homer P Rainy clippings and documents, 1946-2002 (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
- Series XI. Audio/Visual Material
  - John Schere Shares his expressions(?) w/letter, Expression; tr-16757 (Box 52)
  - 5AM Keen NACUC (?), Undated; tr-16758 (Box 52)
  - Brother David Worship, Undated; tr-16759 (Box 52)
  - Linda + Foster Palmer, 1971-05-23; tr-16760 (Box 52)
  - Unlabeled Cassette w/ letter, Undated; tr-16761 (Box 52)
  - "16 Minutes", Undated; tr-16762 (Box 52)
  - Unlabeled unknown Tape, Undated; tr-16763 (Box 52)
  - Bill Hunley tape #3, 1961-02-10; tr-16764 (Box 52)
  - Bill Hunley tape #4, 1961-02-10; tr-16765 (Box 52)
  - Bill Hunley tape #2, 1961-02-10; tr-16766 (Box 52)
  - Come Sweet Death pt I-V, Undated; tr-16767 (Box 52)
  - Bill Hunley tape #1, 1961-02-10; tr-16768 (Box 52)
  - Dialogue- Keep, Undated; tr-16769 (Box 52)
  - Mission Pt I, Undated; tr-16770 (Box 52)
  - Weismann at Laos PMQ Pt 2, Undated; tr-16771 (Box 52)
  - Columbus 17 Harrelson Little, Undated; tr-16772 (Box 52)
  - "Decision," James W. Wogener #1, 1961-10-23; tr-16773 (Box 52)
  - Elaine L- CA 12-19-60 Part II, 1960-12-19; tr-16774 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren Lecture I, Pt I, 1961-02-06; tr-16775 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren Tape 2 CS-IV Lecture 1- Intro to Ethics, 1961-03-27; tr-16776 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren Lecture I, Pt II, 1961-02-06; tr-16777 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren Tape 1 CS-IV Lecture 1 Intro to Ethics, 1961-03-27; tr-16778 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren: Politics 2 CS-IV Tape 1, 1961-04-24; tr-16779 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren: Prophets Pt II CS-III, 1961-03-13; TR-16780 (Box 52)
  - Weisman CH Art Address- Modern Man Pt I, 1969-09-23; tr-16781 (Box 52)
  - Board of Directors Don Weisman- "The New Mood in Art" Pt I, 1960-11; tr-16782 (Box 52)
  - Community Studies 2 Lecture 8 The Christ Event According to John or Human Existence and Truth, Undated; tr-16783 (Box 52)
  - Community Studies 2 Lecture 4- The Christ Event According to the Synoptics or Human Existence and Resurrection- Joe Slicker, Undated; tr-16784 (Box 52)
  - CS 111- Lecture 3 The Reformation and Martin Luther or the Witness of Faith in the End of an Age- Robert Bryant, Undated; tr-16785 (Box 52)
  - CS 2- Lecture 2 The Exodust [sic] Event Part 1- and the Pentateuch, Undated; tr-16786 (Box 52)
  - Fred Gealy- "New Methodology in Biblical Theologizing" Pt 2, 1959; tr-16787 (Box 52)
  - Don Warren Introduction to Fathers, Undated; tr-16788 (Box 52)
  - CSI a, 2 Don Warren Pt 2, 1961-09-25; tr-16789 (Box 52)
  - Cs IA 2 CH, 1961-09-25; tr-16790 (Box 52)
  - CS II Lecture 2- 20th Century Church Warren, 1961-11-13; tr-16791 (Box 52)
  - CS II Lecture 1- 20th Century Church Warren, 1961-11-13; tr-16792 (Box 52)
  - Warren: "Prophets" Part I CS-III, 1961-03-13; tr-16793 (Box 52)
  - CH-CSII Lecture II "Theological Revival in the Church" Warren, 1960-11-21; tr-16794 (Box 52)
  - CH-CSII Lecture II "Theological Revival in the Church" Warren, 1960-11-21; tr-16795 (Box 52)
  - Dr. Handy Art and Science, 1962-04-13; tr-16796 (Box 52)
  - Community Studies 2 Lecture 4- The Christ Event According to the Synoptics or Human Existence and Resurrection- Joe Slicker, 1966-02-19; tr-16797 (Box 52)
  - Community Studies 2 Lecture 3 The Exodus Event and the Pentateuch or Human Existence and Memory Part 2 Bryant, Undated; tr-16798 (Box 52)
  - CS 111 Lecture 7 The Gathered Church Under Corporate Discipline Robert R. Bryant Part 2, Undated; tr-16799 (Box 52)
  - CS 111 Lecture 7 The Gathered Church Under corporate Discipline Robert R Bryant, Undated; tr-16800 (Box 52)
  - Europe- Jay R and JAS II, Undated; tr-16801 (Box 52)
  - Europe- Jay R and JAS III, Undated; tr-16802 (Box 52)
  - CS IV- Lecture 6 The Vocation to be World Citizen AB- Part 1, Undated; tr-16803 (Box 52)
  - Fred Gealy- PMC Fall 59 "New Methodology in Biblical Theologizing", 1959; tr-16804 (Box 53)
  - Fred Gealy- PMC 59 "New Methodology in Biblical Theologizing" Part 4, 1959; tr-16805 (Box 53)
  - Weisman CH Part II Art Address Modern Man, 1960-09-23; tr-16806 (Box 53)
  - Board of Directors Don Weissman- "The New Mood in Art" Part III, 1960-11; tr-16807 (Box 53)
  - Board of Directors Don Weissman- "The New Mood in Art" Part II, 1960-11; tr-16808 (Box 53)
  - HRN Lecture 2 "Faith of the Common Life", Undated; tr-16809 (Box 53)
  - HRN Lecture 3 "Faith and Hope", Undated; tr-16810 (Box 53)
  - Weisman CH Part III, 1960-09-23; tr-16811 (Box 53)
  - Unlabeled Tape, Undated; tr-16812 (Box 53)
  - CH Friday Night Worship Warren- The Symbol and Cultic Ritual, 1960-09-30; tr-16813 (Box 53)
  - Weisman Part I Contemporary Art, Undated; tr-16814 (Box 53)
  - CH Friday Nite "The Symbol and Cultic Time", 1960-12-02; tr-16815 (Box 53)
  - CH Friday Nite "The Symbol and Cultic Time" Part II, 1960-12-02; tr-16816 (Box 53)
  - CS1 Lecture 11 Part 1 The Illusion of Life, Undated; tr-16817 (Box 53)
  - CS1 Lecture 11 Part 2 The Illusions of Life, Undated; tr-16818 (Box 53)
  - Don Warren Friday Nite Baptism, 1961-03-10; tr-16819 (Box 53)
  - Don Warren Friday Nite Baptism Very Short, 1961-03-10; tr-16820 (Box 53)
  - Unlabeled Tape, Undated; tr-16821 (Box 53)
  - Community Studies 2 Lecture 8 The Christ Event According to John or Human Existence and Truth, Undated; tr-16822 (Box 53)
  - Fred Gealy "New Methodology in Biblical Theologizing" Part 3, 1959; tr-16823 (Box 53)
  - Curriculum Studies III Lecture IV The Great Awakening and John Wesley or the Witness of Faith in the Era of Rationalism Part 2, Undated; tr-16824 (Box 53)
  - Curriculum Studies III Lecture IV The Great Awakening and John Wesley or the Witness of Faith in the Era of Rationalism Part 1, Undated; tr-16825 (Box 53)
  - Allen Brockway CS III 6,1 Part II, 1961-03-06; tr-16826 (Box 53)
  - Allen Brockway CS III 6,1 Part II, 1961-03-06; tr-16827 (Box 53)
  - CS IV- Lecture 6 The Vocation to be World Citizen AB- Part 2, Undated; tr-16828 (Box 53)
  - CH Friday Night Wayne Holzman Psychology Part I, 1960-1961; tr-16829 (Box 53)
  - Unlabeled Tape, Undated; tr-16830 (Box 53)
  - Dr. WT Guy: The 20th Century Scientific Revolution, 1961-11-13; tr-16831 (Box 53)
  - Dr. WT Guy The 20th Century Scientific Revolution, 1961-11-13; tr-16832 (Box 53)
  - Dr. WT Guy The 20th Century Scientific Revolution, 1961-11-13; tr-16833 (Box 53)
  - CH Conversation Rosalie Oaks South Africa, 1961-11-28; tr-16834 (Box 53)
  - Don Weismann New Image of Man in Art, 1960-10; tr-16835 (Box 53)
  - Curriculum Studies 2 Lecture 2 The Christ Even and the Church or Human Existence and Community Part 1, Undated; tr-16836 (Box 53)
  - Curriculum Studies 2 Lecture 2 The Christ Even and the Church or Human Existence and Community Part 2, Undated; tr-16837 (Box 53)
  - Art Brandenburg CMS tape 2, Undated; tr-16838 (Box 53)
  - Bob Terry, 1962-04-27; tr-16839 (Box 53)
  - Weismann New Image of Man in Art Part II, 1960-10; tr-16840 (Box 53)
  - Unlabeled Tape, Undated; tr-16841 (Box 54)
  - Don Warren Introduction to Church Fathers Pt II, 1960-1961; tr-16842 (Box 54)
  - Wayne Holtzman Psychology Part III, 1960-1961; tr-16843 (Box 54)
  - Europe Joy P and JAS-1, Undated; tr-16844 (Box 54)
  - Joe Slicker, Undated; tr-16845 (Box 54)
  - Columbus 10 Harrelson discussion, Undated; tr-16846 (Box 54)
  - Doc Wagner, Undated; tr-16847 (Box 54)
  - Don Warren, 1962-04-16; tr-16848 (Box 54)
  - Theodore Matson, Undated; tr-16849 (Box 54)
  - Bill Smith Prophet, Priest, and Chosen People, 1962-03-12; tr-16850 (Box 54)
  - Unlabeled Tape, Undated; tr-16851 (Box 54)
  - Europe- Joy P and JAS IV, Undated; tr-16852 (Box 54)
  - Doris Neal: Memory and the Chosen People, 1962-03-19; tr-16853 (Box 54)
  - HRN Lecture 1 "Reasoning Faith", Undated; tr-16854 (Box 54)
  - Curriculum Studies III Lecture VI- The Gathered Church at Corporate Worship and Study Part 2 Joseph A Slicker, Undated; tr-16855 (Box 54)
  - Curriculum Studies III Lecture VI- The Gathered Church at Corporate Worship and Study Part 1 Joseph A Slicker, Undated; tr-16856 (Box 54)
  - JAS: Educational Order CS-IV, 1961-05-01; tr-16857 (Box 54)
  - JAS: The Sacraments: Enchanted Friday Dinner Service Tape 1, 1961-02-17; tr-16858 (Box 54)
  - CS II "New Image of the Church" Part II JAS, 1960-11-14; tr-16859 (Box 54)
  - "The Ambiguity of Life or Decisiveness Through X", 1960-10-24; tr-16860 (Box 54)
  - "New Image of the Church", 1960-11-14; tr-16861 (Box 54)
  - Lecture III JAS X-event, 1960-10-03; tr-16862 (Box 54)
  - Lecture III JAS X-event, 1960-10-03; tr-16863 (Box 54)
  - "The Ambiguity of Life" Lecture VI Part II, 1960-10-24; tr-16864 (Box 54)
  - CH CS-1 Lecture 2 Crisis of Life JAS, 1960-1961; tr-16865 (Box 54)
  - CH CSI Lecture 2 JAS, 1960-1961; tr-16866 (Box 54)
  - Lecture VII The Illusions of Life JAS Part 1, 1960-1961; tr-16867 (Box 54)
  - Lecture VII The Illusions of Life JAS Part 2, 1960-1961; tr-16868 (Box 54)
  - CS Lecture 8 JAS: The Penatence Part 2, Undated; tr-16869 (Box 54)
  - JAS: The Pentatence CS III Lecture 8 Part 1, Undated; tr-16870 (Box 54)
  - CS 2- Lecture 7 The Exodus Event in the Writing JAS Part 1, Undated; tr-16871 (Box 54)
  - CS 2- Lecture 7 The Exodus Event and the Writing JAS Part 2, Undated; tr-16872 (Box 54)
  - CH CS II Lecture VIII Augustine JAS, 1961-01-09; tr-16873 (Box 54)
  - CH CS II Lecture VIII Augustine JAS, 1961-01-09; tr-16874 (Box 54)
  - CH Fall 1960 JAS "Disciplined Community" Part II, 1960; tr-16875 (Box 54)
  - CH CS II Lecture JAS "Disciplined Community", 1960; tr-16876 (Box 54)
  - California Tour Tape 2, Undated; tr-16877 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 102-103, Undated; tr-16878 (Box 54)
  - Rancho Verde, 1973-10-11; tr-16879 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 1, Undated; tr-16880 (Box 54)
  - California Tape 4, Undated; tr-16881 (Box 54)
  - Tape 114-115, Undated; tr-16882 (Box 54)
  - Californina Tour 113, Undated; tr-16883 (Box 54)
  - Omlene Roses Continued, 1973-10-12; tr-16884 (Box 54)
  - California Tour, Undated; tr-16885 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 110-111, Undated; tr-16886 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 101, Undated; tr-16887 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 3, Undated; tr-16888 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 104, Undated; tr-16889 (Box 54)
  - California Seabreeze, 1973-10-17; tr-16890 (Box 54)
  - Leone Anaheim, 1973-10-12; tr-16891 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 5, Undated; tr-16892 (Box 54)
  - Tour of the Salinos, 1973-10-15; tr-16893 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 108, Undated; tr-16894 (Box 54)
  - San Diego Zoo 110, Undated; tr-16895 (Box 54)
  - California Tour 106-107, Undated; tr-16896 (Box 54)
  - Ted Hughes Suicide Collection, Undated; tr-16897 (Box 54)
  - The Gift of Song, Undated; tr-16898 (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Undated (Box 54)
  - CH CS II Lecture VII Aquinas JWM Part 1, 1961-01-04; tr-16899 (Box 55)
  - CSII Lecture IV, JWM "Mission and Corporate Action" Tape 1, 1960-1961; tr-16900 (Box 55)
  - Eddie Shaw - Friday Nite The Church on Campus, 1961-05-05; tr-16901 (Box 55)
  - Group III Session II Lecture III Christian Education JWM Tape I, 1960-11; tr-16902 (Box 55)
  - PMC Group III Session II Lecture III Christian Education Tape II, 1960-11; tr-16903 (Box 55)
  - Discussing The Relativity: What is Christian? Tape 4, tr-16904 (Box 55)
  - Matthews Part 2, 1957-10-21; tr-16905 (Box 55)
  - Matthews Part 1, 1957-10-21; tr-16906 (Box 55)
  - CS II Lecture IV JWM "Mission and Corporate Action" Tape II, 1960-1961; tr-16907 (Box 55)
  - JWM: Life in Faith Affirmation III in Negatives/College House, 1957-10; tr-16908 (Box 55)
  - CS II Lecture VUU Aquinas JWM Part II, 1961-01-04; tr-16909 (Box 55)
  - JWM The Mission and the Faith", Undated; tr-16910 (Box 55)
  - JWM Education in the Church Part 2, 1959-06-09; tr-16911 (Box 55)
  - Community Studies I Lecture 9 The Affirmation of Life or the Christ Spirit, Undated; tr-16912 (Box 55)
  - Joe Slicker: Synaptics Tape 1, 1961-02-13; tr-16913 (Box 55)
  - Joe Slicker: Synaptics Tape 2, 1961-02-13; tr-16914 (Box 55)
  - Campus Ministers' Symposium Campus Church as Mission in its Gatheredness or the New Discipline on Campus- Joe Slicker, Undated; tr-16915 (Box 55)
  - Campus Ministers' Symposium Campus Church as Mission in its Gatheredness or the New Discipline on Campus- Joe Slicker Part 1, Undated; tr-16916 (Box 55)
  - Lecture 3 The Limit of Life Part 1, Undated; tr-16917 (Box 55)
  - CS-1 Lecture 3 The Limit of Life Part 2, Undated; tr-16918 (Box 55)
  - CS II Lecture V The Scattered Church as Mission in the World Part 2 Joseph A Slicker, Undated; tr-16919 (Box 55)
  - CS III Lecture V The Scattered Church as Mission in the World Part I Joseph A Slicker, Undated; tr-16920 (Box 55)
  - Lecture 1 The Possibility for (missing)FE Part 1, Undated; tr-16921 (Box 55)
  - CS 1 Lecture 5 The Possibility for Life JAS Part 2, Undated; tr-16922 (Box 55)
  - CS 1 Lecture 8 Part 1 The Styles of Life, Undated; tr-16923 (Box 55)
  - CS 1 Lecture 8 The Styles of Life or the Christ-Faith, Undated; tr-16924 (Box 55)
  - CS 1 Lecture 10 Part 2 The Ambiguities of Life, Undated; tr-16925 (Box 55)
  - CS 1 Lecture 10 Part 1 The Ambiguities of Life, Undated; tr-16926 (Box 55)
  - PMC (ADV) The Little Church in the Great Church tape 1, 1960-10; tr-16927 (Box 55)
  - PMC (ADV) The Little Church in the Great Church tape 1, 1960-10; tr-16928 (Box 55)
  - JAS: The Sacraments: Eucharist Friday Dinner Service Tape 2, 1961-02-17; tr-15863 (Box 55)
  - Board of Directors JAS The New Breakthrough for Mission Part 1, 1960-11; tr-15864 (Box 55)
  - Board of Directors JAS The New Breakthrough for Mission Part 2, 1960-11; tr-15865 (Box 55)
  - CS III Lecture 1 The Ancient Church and St. Augustine Part 2 JAS, Undated; tr-15866 (Box 55)
  - CS III Lecture 1 The Ancient Church and St. Augustine Part 1 JAS, Undated; tr-15867 (Box 55)